[MUSIC PLAYING]
Fulfillment by Amazon or FBA is a great way
to grow your business and reach more customers.
With FBA, Amazon stores your inventory,
ships your orders, and handles returns, and customer service.
Your FBA products also become eligible for free shipping
and Amazon Prime 2-day delivery.
This is a great way to maximize exposure and sales
in the Amazon store.
Sellers new to FBA can also enroll in the FBA New Selection
Program.
The FBA New Selection Program includes free monthly storage,
removals, and return processing for all eligible
new to FBA parent ASINs.
Plus, new FBA sellers can receive credits and discounts
for things like advertising and shopping.
Your FBA costs will depend on the products you sell
and the exact services you use.
You may also encounter fees related
to storing and managing your FBA inventory.
There are three tools you can use
to estimate your potential FBA fees in Seller Central.
The estimated fee per unit sold column
on the FBA inventory page.
The revenue calculator and the fee preview report.
To learn more about calculating your potential FBA fees,
you can review our guide, "Is FBA Right for You?"
in Seller Central.